邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural.
那晚发生的事
What happened that night.
赶快带你弟弟出去
Take your brother outside as fast as you can!
快 迪恩 快跑
Now, Dean! Go!
他们亲眼目睹
What they witnessed.
玛丽 不
Mary! No!
两兄弟
Sent two brothers.
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅
Dad is on a hunting trip…
他好几天没回家了
and he hasn't been home in a few days.
从此踏上征途 22年后
On a quest for answers. 22 years later.
我发过誓我再也不猎魔了
I swore I was done hunting.
我一个人不行
I can't do this alone.
不
No!
我们有活儿干了
We've got work to do.
这是爸爸最最有价值的东西
This is dad's single, most valuable possession.
他所有知道的关于恶魔的东西都记载在这里面
Everything he knows about every evil thing, it is in here.
我觉得他想让我们继续他的工作
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
你知道 拯救人类 猎杀恶魔
You know, saving people, hunting things.
家族事业
Family business.
不 我得找出杀杰西卡的凶手
No. I gotta find Jessica's killer.
这是我现在唯一想做的事
This is the only thing I can think about.
萨姆 你知道我们会找到爸爸的 是吧
Sam, you know that we're gonna find dad, yeah?
是的
Yeah.
《邪恶力量》
（托莱多 俄亥俄州）
好了 轮到你了真心话还是大冒险
Okay, your turn. Truth or dare?
真心话
Truth.
你想和本杰·斯沃茨约会吗
Do you wanna make outwith Benjy Swartz?
- 大冒险 - 那好吧
- Dare. - Okay, lame.
胆小鬼你必须…
You have to…
在浴室里说 镜子巫婆
say "Bloody Mary" in the bathroom.
这是你能想到的最好的主意
Is that the bestyou can come up with?
谁是 镜子巫婆
Who's Bloody Mary?
她是个巫婆
She's this witch.
我听说她死于车祸
I heard she was a ladykilled in a car crash.
她是谁不重要
It doesn't matter who she is.
只要你在浴室里说三次 她的名字
Point is, if you say her name three timesin the bathroom mirror…
她就会出现… 。-
she appears…
把你的眼睛挖出来
and scratches your eyes out!
为什么没人提到这些呢
So why would anyone say it?
因为那是假的
Because it isn't real.
别开灯
No turning on the lights.
记住 要说三次哦
three times.
镜子巫婆
Bloody Mary.
这太愚蠢了
This is so stupid.
镜子巫婆
Bloody Mary.
- 吓着你了吧 - 你们太可恶了
- Scared you. - You guys are jerks.
对不起 爸爸
Sorry, Daddy.
对不起 鞋匠先生
GIRLSSorry, Mr. Shoemaker.
你这么喜欢他啊
You so like him.
嘿 女孩们 玩的挺开心哦
Hey, geek.You guys having fun?
你们回来的太晚了
You're out past curfew.
知道了 爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
啊 萨姆
Why, Sam?
不
No!
萨姆 萨姆
Why, Sam? Why, Sam?
萨姆 醒醒
Sam, wake up!
我想我是在做噩梦
Take it I was having a nightmare.
是的 一个接一个
Yeah. Another one.
嘿 至少我小睡了会
Hey, at least I got some sleep.
我们迟早得谈谈这个
Sooner or later, we're gonna have to talk about this.
- 我们到了吗 - 是
- We're here? - Yep.
恩 欢迎来到托莱多。-俄亥俄州
Welcome to Toledo, Ohio.
你认为在这个家伙身上 到底发生了什么事
What do you thinkhappened to this guy?
这正是我们要去查清楚的
That's what we're gonna find out.
来吧
Let's go.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 我能为你做些什么吗 - 恩 我们是
- Can I help you? - Yeah, we're the…
医学院的学生
med students.
- 对不起 - 噢 菲葛拉维奇
- Sorry? - Oh, Doctor…
医生没告诉你吗
Feiklowicz didn't tell you?
我们和他在电话里谈过了
We talked to him on the phone. He.
我们来自俄亥俄州
We're from Ohio State.
他让我们查看一下鞋匠的尸体 为了我们的论文
He's supposed to show usthe Shoemaker corpse. For our paper.
- 喔 对不起 他现在在吃午饭 - 哦
- Well, l'm sorry. He's at lunch. - Oh.
是这样 他说… 。-这也没什么关系的
Well, he said-Well, you know, it doesn't matter.
- 你可以让我们看看尸体吗 - 对不起我不能那么做
- You don't mind showing us the body? - Sorry, I can't.
他会在一个小时内回来 如果你们愿意 可以在这等他
Doc will be back in an hour.You can wait for him, if you want.
一个小时 哦
An hour? Ooh.
可我们得马上回哥伦布
We gotta be heading backto Columbus by then.
听着 伙计这个论文要占我们成绩的一半
Look, this paper's half our grade.
- 你不会介意帮帮我们吧 - 伙计
- So if you don't mind helping us out. - Look, man.
这不行
No.
我想揍扁这家伙
I'm gonna hit him in his face, I swear-
跟我来吧
Follow me.
兄弟 这可是我赢的钱
Dude, I earned that money.
你打牌赢来的钱
You won it in a poker game.
是的
Yeah.
报纸上说是他女儿找到他
Now, the newspaper saidhis daughter found him.
她说他的眼睛在流血
She said his eyes were bleeding.
不止那样 他的眼睛被溶化了
More than that.They practically liquefied.
有任何搏斗的迹象吗
Any sign of a struggle?
- 或许是某人做的 - 不
- Maybe somebody did it to him? - Nope.
除了他的女儿就没别的人了
Besides the daughter, he was all alone.
官方对于死亡的解释是什么
What's the official cause of death?
医生也不太确定 他觉得可能因为动脉瘤
Doc's not sure.He's thinking massive stroke…
而导致大出血
maybe an aneurysm.
但可以肯定的是是脑内部被破坏了
Something burst up in there, that's for sure.
- 你的意思 - 剧烈脑部出血
- What do you mean? - lntense cerebral bleeding.
我从没看到别人的头颅上有他这么多的血迹
This guy had more blood in his skullthan anyone l've ever seen.
但那双眼睛 是怎么回事呢
But the eyes.What would cause something like that?
毛细血管会突然破裂
Capillaries can burst.
很多人死的时候眼睛也流血
A lot of bloodshot eyeswith stroke victims.
恩 你是否曾经看过和这一样的眼睛吗
Yeah, you ever see exploding eyeballs?
我也是头一回看见
That's a first for me.
但是 我可不是医生
But, hey, l'm not the doctor.
我们能看看警方的验尸报告吗
Hey, think we could lookat the police report?
你也明白的 这是为了我们的论文
You know, for our paper.
我真的不能把报告给你们看
I'm not really supposed toshow you that.
可能不是恶鬼做的 只是比较奇怪的医学事件
Might not be one of ours.Might just be some freak medical thing.
那在老爸的常年的抓鬼工作中有哪次真是怪异的医学事件
How many times in Dad's long careerhas it been a freak medical thing…
而不是灵异鬼怪事件吗
and not some sign ofawful supernatural death?
好象从来没有
Almost never.
- 没错 - 那好
- Exactly. - All right.
让我们和他女儿谈谈
Let's go talk to the daughter.
我们好象穿得不太合适
I feel like we're underdressed.
- 你一定就是唐娜 是吗 - 是的
- You must be Donna, right? - Yeah.
- 嗨 我们真的对此很抱歉 - 谢谢你
- Hi. We're really sorry. - Thank you.
我是萨姆 这是迪恩
I'm Sam. This is Dean.
我们是你爸的同事
We worked with your dad.
- 真的吗 - 是的 这整件事…
- You did? - Yeah. This whole thing…
我觉得这是突然中风
I mean, a stroke.
- 我觉得她可能不想说起这些 - 没关系我没事
- I don't think she really wants to talk. - It's okay. l'm okay.
事发之前有什么症状吗 有头昏眼花 偏头痛吗
Were there ever any symptoms?Dizziness? Migraines?
没有
No.
- 是因为这根本就不是中风 - 莉莉 别乱说话
- That's because it wasn't a stroke. - Lily, don't say that.
- 什么 - 不好意思她有点心烦
- What? - l'm sorry. She's just upset.
不 这全是因为我
No, it happened because of me.
- 亲爱的 不是那样 - 莉莉
- Sweetie, it didn't. - Lily…
为什么你会这么说
why would you saysomething like that?
在他死前 我曾经说过
Right before he died, I said it.
- 你说了什么 - 「血腥码丽」
- You said what? - "Bloody Mary."
对着浴室的镜子说了三遍
Three times in the bathroom mirror.
她拿走了他的眼睛 她的确是这样做的
She took his eyes.That's what she does.
但那不是爸爸致死的原因 这不是你的错
That's not why Dad died.This isn't your fault.
我觉得你姐姐说的对 莉莉
I think your sister's right, Lily.
根本就没血腥码丽这种东西
There's no wayit could've been Bloody Mary.
你父亲没那么说过
I mean, your dad didn't say it.
是吗
Did he?
恩 我想也许我错了
No, I don't think so.
关于血腥码丽的传说
The Bloody Mary Legend.
爸爸以前有找到过能证明这事的证据吗
Dad ever find any evidencethat it was a real thing?
据我所知没有
Not that I know of.
我也知道 在其他地方
I mean, everywhere else…
这个国家的很多孩子都在玩血腥码丽这个游戏
all over the country, kids play Bloody Mary…
据我们所知 没人因此而死
and as far as we know, nobody dies from it.
也可能在其它地方那只是个故事
Maybe everywhere it's a story, but here it's actually happening.
但在这却真实地发生了
The place where the legend began?
可能这是传说开始的地点
But according to the legend, the person who says.
但根据传说那个…
The person who saysyou-know-what gets it.
- 但在这里是的 - 鞋匠没那么做却…
- But here… - Shoemaker gets it instead.
对
Right.
从没听说这样的事
Never heard anything like that before.
而且这个人是死在镜子前面
Still, the guy did dieright in front of the mirror.
她小女儿话是对的 按传说来说的话
And the daughter's right.The way the legend goes…
你知道谁来挖走了你的眼睛
you-know-who scratchesyour eyes out.
这值得一查
It's worth checking in to.
你们在楼上做什么
What are you doing up here?
我们… 我们想上厕所
We-We had to go to the bathroom.
你们是谁
Who are you?
就像我在楼下所说的我们和唐娜是父亲的同事
Like we said downstairs, we work with Donna's dad.
可他只是一个销售员 他自己一个人工作
He was a day trader or something.He worked by himself.
不 我都知道只是… …
No, I know. I meant.
还有在楼下问的那些古怪的问题
And all thoseweird questions downstairs.
这是为什么
What was that?
你们向我做出解释不然我就要叫人了
So you tell me what's going on, or I start screaming.
那好吧
All right.
我们认为唐娜的爸爸死于某种原因
We think something happenedto Donna's dad.
对啊 中风
Yeah, a stroke.
那不是中风的典型症状
That's not the sign of a typical stroke.
我们认为还有其它原因
We think it might be something else.
- 比如 - 老实说
- Like what? - Honestly…
我们现在也不知道
we don't know yet.
但我们不希望这发生在其他人身上
But we don't want itto happen to anyone else.
事实就是这样
That's the truth.
所以如果你真的想叫的话
So if you're gonna scream…
那随你便
go right ahead.
你们是谁 是警察吗
Who are you, cops?
- 差不多吧 - 我要告诉你
- Something like that. - Tell you what.
要是你一想起什么
Here. You think of anything…
你或者你的朋友发现奇怪的事 超乎寻常的事
you or your friends noticeanything strange, out of the ordinary…
请给我们打电话
just give us a call.
如果这个镇上真有召唤镜子巫婆的话
Say Bloody Mary really ishaunting this town.
那就一定有某些证据
There's gonna be some proof, right?
例如当地一个死的很恐怖的女人
A local woman who died nasty.
但根据传说来这实在太麻烦了
But a legend this widespread, it's hard.
关于她的身份大概有50种说法
There's like 50 versionsof who she is.
有些说她是个女巫另一写说
One says she's a witch, another says…
她是个遇害的新娘 还有其他一大堆说法
she's a mutilated bride.There's a lot more.
那我们应该去寻找什么
So, what are we looking for?
关于她的每个版本有个共同点 她是个叫玛丽的女人
Every version's got things in common.It's always a woman named Mary.
她死在镜子前面
And she always diesright in front of a mirror.
所以我们该去找找当地的报纸 在那些公众信息里
We gotta search newspapers, public records, as far back as they go…
看看我们是否能找到个符合条件的玛丽
see if we can find a Marywho fits the bill.
- 这么找太烦人了 - 不 这没什么的… …
- Well, that sounds annoying. - No, it won't be so bad…
只要我们
as long as we…
我收回我的话 真是很烦啊
Huh, I take it back.This will be very annoying.
我也不清楚 他们是警察侦探或者是其他什么的
I'm not sure. They were copsor detectives or something.
管他们是什么不过他们长的挺帅的
Whoever they were, they were cute.
吉尔 你不那么想吗
Jill. You didn't think so?
是的 他们是帅哥
Yeah, okay, they were cute, but still…
但是 你不觉得在唐娜的父亲身上可能真的有些奇怪的事发生
do you think something could havehappened to Donna's dad?
也许 莉莉是对的
Maybe Lily was right.
也许是镜子巫婆做的
Maybe Bloody Mary got him.
哈哈 听上去好有趣哦
Ha, ha. Very funny.
等等 对不起 我听出来你很害怕
Wait, l'm sorry.Was that fear I hear in your voice?
没有查理…
No.
我现在要走到浴室的镜子前了
l'm walkingto the bathroom mirror right now.
吉尔 别那么做
Jill, quit it.
噢 不 我控制不了我自己
Oh, no. I can't help myself.
我要说出口了
I'm gonna say it.
镜子巫婆 镜子巫婆
Bloody Mary, Bloody Mary…
镜子巫婆
Bloody Mary.
吉尔
Jill?
Jill!
你这个胆小鬼我明天打给你
You're such a freak.I'll call you tomorrow.
是你干的
You did it.
你杀了那个男孩
You killed that boy.
为什么 萨姆
Why, Sam?
你为什么要让我睡着
Why'd you let me fall asleep?
因为我是你大哥
Because I'm an awesome brother.
你梦到什么
So, what did you dream about?
棒棒糖和糖果
Lollipops and candy canes.
哦 是吗
Yeah, sure.
你找到什么吗
You find anything?
一无所获 另外一个全新的挫折
Oh, besides a whole new levelof frustration?
什么也没 我看了相关的所有资料
No. I've looked at everything.
当地的女人 叫劳拉的或叫凯瑟琳的 在镜前自杀
A few local women, Laura and Cathryn, committed suicide in front of a mirror.
还有一个巨大的镜子掉在一个叫戴夫男孩身上 可是
And a giant mirror fell ona guy named Dave, but…
没有 玛丽这个人
no Mary.
也许是我们还没找到她
Maybe we just haven't found it yet.
I've also been searching forstrange deaths in the area.
你知道吗 我也找寻了这个区域内的奇怪的死亡事件 没有什么
You know, eyeball bleeding, that sort of thing. There's nothing.
这里到底发生了什么事也许根本就没有玛丽
Whatever's happening heremaybe just aingt Mary.
你好
Hello?
他们在浴室的地板上找到了她
And they found heron the bathroom floor.
她… 。-她的眼睛
And her-Her eyes.
它们不见了
They were gone.
我很难过
I'm sorry.
她说出了那些话
And she said it.
我听到她说了
I heard her say it.
可是不可能就因为那样她就死了
But it couldn't be because of that.
也许我想法不太正常 对吗
I'm insane, right?
不 你想法很正常
No, you're not insane.
天啊 这让我感觉更糟糕
God, that makes me feelso much worse.
听着…
Look.
我们认为这里有某些事发生
We think something's happening here.
某些不能解释的事情
Something that can't be explained.
但我们必须阻止它
And we're gonna stop it.
所以我们需要你的帮助
But we could use your help.
你和吉尔的妈妈怎么说的
What did you tell Jill's mom?
我只是说我想单独来看看吉尔的照片和物品
I just said I needed some time alonewith Jill's pictures and things.
我讨厌向她撒谎
I hate lying to her.
相信我们这是为了大家好 关灯
Trust us, it's for the greater good.Hit the lights.
你们在找什么
What are you guys looking for?
我们一找到就让你知道
We'll let you knowas soon as we find it.
夜视模式
Hey, night vision.
谢谢 很好
Thanks. Perfect.
我看上去象琶里斯·希尔顿吗
Do I look like Paris Hilton?
我些不明白 我是指第一个被害人
So I don't get it.I mean, the first victim…
并没有召唤玛丽 但第二个被害人却那么做了
didn't summon Mary, and the second victim did.
她是怎么选上他的
How is she choosing them?
我也不清楚
Beats me.
我想知道为什么吉尔会说出那个名字
I wanna know whyJill said it in the first place.
那只是个玩笑
It was just a joke.
一定有人还会说出那个名字 那只是时间问题
Well, somebody's gonna say it again.It's just a matter of time.
嘿
Hey.
箱子里有夜光的东西 是吗
There's a black lightin the trunk, right?
加里·不莱曼
Gary Bryman?
你知道他是谁吗
You know who that is?
不
No.
加里·不莱曼是个8岁的男孩
So Gary Brymanwas an 8-year-old boy.
两年前 他在跑闹中被撞死司机肇事后逃逸
Two years ago, he was killed in a hit-and-run.
是辆黑色的丰田车
The car was described asa black Toyota Camry…
可没人有照片也没人看到驾驶员
but nobody got the platesor saw the driver.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
- 什么 - 吉尔 就开那种车
- What? - Jill drove that car.
我们需要再去一次你朋友唐娜的家
We need to getto your friend Donna's house.
鞋匠琳达
Linda Shoemaker.
你们为什么要来问我这个
Why are you asking me this?
听着 不好意思可这真的很重要
Look, we're sorry, but it's important.
是的 琳达是我妈妈
Yeah. Linda's my mom, okay?
她服用了过量的安眠药
And she overdosed on sleeping pills.
那是一场意外 就是这样
It was an accident, and that's it.
- 我想你们该走了 - 唐娜 听我说
- I think you should leave. - Donna, just-
给我滚出我的房子
Just get out of my house!
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
你们认为她父亲杀害了她的母亲
Do you really think her dadcould've killed her mom?
可能
Maybe.
我想我得留下来陪她
I think I should stick around.
好的 无论你想怎样 但不能… 。-
All right. Whatever you do, don't…
相信我 我不会说出去的
Believe me, I won't say it.
等等 你进行全国性的搜索
Wait, wait, wait.You're doing a nationwide search?
是的美国联邦调查局里所有数据
Yep. The NClC, the FBI database.
找到在国内任何死在镜子前的玛丽对我来说都行
At this point, any Mary who died in frontof a mirror is good enough for me.
但如果她在这个镇里作乱的话 她就应该是死于这个镇
But if she's haunting the town, she should've died in the town.
我告诉过你当地的资料里什么都没有 除非你有更好的主意
There's nothing local.Unless you got a better idea…
- 好象有着某条线索 - 我也不清楚我也在想这个
- lt seems like there's a pattern. - I was thinking the same thing.
鞋匠和吉尔的肇事逃逸
Mr. Shoemaker and Jill's hit-and-run.
都有关于某人死亡的秘密对
Both had secrets where people died.
关于镜子民间有很多传说 它们揭露你的谎言
There's folklore about mirrors.They reveal your lies…
你的秘密 你真实灵魂的反映
your secrets.They're a true reflection of your soul…
打破它你会很倒霉
which is why it's bad luckto break them.
不错 不错
Right, right.
所以假如是你有着这样的秘密
So maybe if you've got a secret.
比如别人的死与你有关
like a real nasty one.
然后 玛丽
then Mary sees it…
就会看到这个秘密并且惩罚你
and punishes you for it.
不管你是否召唤她
Whether you summoned her or not.
看看这个
Take a look at this.
看着很象同样的手印
Looks like the same handprint.
她叫玛丽·华辛顿
Her name was Mary Worthington.
在韦恩堡。-印第安纳州死于谋杀至今未能结案
An unsolved murder inFort Wayne, Indiana.
我做这个工作35年了
I was on the job for 35 years.
大部分做侦探工作
Detective for most of that.
现在 可能所有人都不太记起那个案件
Now, everybody packs it inwith a few loose ends.
但这起 玛丽·华辛顿的谋杀案
But the Mary Worthington murder…
我还是记忆犹新
that one still gets me.
到底发生了什么
What exactly happened?
你们自称是记者
You boys said you were reporters.
据我们所知 玛丽19岁独自一个人
We know Mary was 19, lived by herself.
她赢了一些选美比赛 梦想走出印地安那
She won a few beauty contests.Dreamt of getting out of lndiana…
成为一个演员 在5月29日 晚上
being an actress.And we know the night of March 29th…
有人闯进了她的房间 杀害了她
someone broke into her apartmentand murdered her.
用刀挖出了她的眼睛
Cut out her eyes with a knife.
没错
That's right.
你看 先生 我们问你发生了什么
When we ask you what happened, we wanna know what…
我们是想问你关于这案件的想法
you think happened.
一般来说 我不应该有这样的复印件
Technically, l'm notsupposed to have a copy of this.
现在
Now…
看这里
see that there?
- T-R-E - 恩
- "T-R-E"? - Yeah.
我想玛丽想拼出杀害她凶手的名字
I think Mary was trying tospell the name of her killer.
- 你知道他是谁吗 - 不确定
- You know who it was? - Not for sure.
但这有个当地的外科医生
But there was a local man, a surgeon.
特雷弗·桑浦森
Trevor Samson.
我觉得是他干的
And I think he cut her up good.
为什么他会那么做
Now, why would he dosomething like that?
她的日记里提到了她遇到的一个男人
Her diary mentioneda man that she was seeing.
她用他名字的第一个字母 T称呼他
She called him by his initial, T.
她的最后一篇日记
Well, her last entry…
她将要告诉T的老婆他们间的事情
she was gonna tell T's wifeall about their affair.
可你怎么断定是桑浦森杀害了她
But how do you know it wasthis guy Samson who killed her?
这很难说
It's hard to say.
但她眼睛被挖出来的方式 手法很专业
But the way her eyes were cut out, it was almost professional.
可你没法证明是他杀的
But you could never prove it?
是的 没有指纹 没有目击证人
No. No prints, no witnesses.
他很小心翼翼
He was meticulous.
他还活着吗
Is he still alive?
不
Nope.
就向你们问我的 玛丽用她生命的最后时刻
If you ask me, Mary spent her last living moments…
去揭示这个家伙的秘密
trying to expose this guy's secret.
但她没法做到了
But she never could.
她埋葬在哪里
Where's she buried?
没有 她被火化了
She wasn't. She was cremated.
这面镜子呢 它没被做为证据锁在某处 是吧
What about that mirror?It's not in some evidence lockup, is it?
是的
No.
很久前就被退还给玛丽的家族
It was returned to Mary's familya long time ago.
你有他们家族的名字吗
You have the names of her family, by any chance?
你把这些陌生人带到我家里
You bring these strangers into my houseand they ask me things like that?
他们还向我提出那样的问题 他们只是想帮你
They were only trying to help.
求你了 唐娜 你得相信我
Please.Donna, you have to believe me.
相信什么 关于镜子巫婆
What? About Bloody Mary?
求你了 我知道这听上去很疯狂
Please. I know it sounds crazy.
真的只是疯狂吗
Crazy doesn't even begin to cover it.
对我妹妹来说 可以相信这些假话 她只有12岁
It's one thing for my sisterto believe this crap. She's 12.
可是你
But you?
想想你爸爸是怎么死的 想想吉尔是怎么死的
But the way your dad died, okay?And the way Jill died.
好吧 那么 镜子巫婆
Okay, so Bloody Mary…
- 不 - 镜子巫婆 镜子巫婆
- No! - …Bloody Mary, Bloody Mary.
看 没事发生
See? Nothing happened.
你为什么那么做
Why would you do that?
天那
Oh, my God.
你真的有病
There really is somethingwrong with you.
原子在失去电子后就会变成阳离子
Elements that lose electronsbecome positive ions…
比起同元素的其它粒子要小
which are smaller than other atomsof the same element.
就是说 它的半径小于其它的粒子
Therefore, the ionic radius is smallerthan the atomic radius.
查理
Charlie!
查理 停下来 怎么拉冷静一点
Charlie, stop it! What's wrong?Just calm down.
让我走查理
Let me go!Charlie!
哦 真的吗 那可太糟糕了 华辛顿先生
Oh, really?That's too bad, Mr. Worthington.
看来我得出高价才能买下那镜子了
I would've paid a lot for that mirror.
好吧 等下次有机会 好的 谢谢你
Okay. Well, maybe next time.All right, thanks.
- 怎么了 - 那是玛丽的兄弟
- So? - So that was Mary's brother.
家族保留了那面镜子许多年直到他几个星期前把它卖了
The mirror was in the family for yearsuntil he sold it.
一星期前
One week ago.
一家叫ESTATE的古董店 在拖莱多
To a store called Estate Antiques.A store in Toledo.
所以说镜子到哪里玛丽也去哪里
So wherever the mirror goes, Mary goes?
她的魂魄肯定和镜子有某种联系
Her spirit's definitelytied up with it somehow.
不是有迷信说镜子可以抓住魂魄吗
Isn't there an old superstition that saysmirrors can capture spirits?
当有人在房间里死去
When someonewould die in a house…
人们会用镜子遮盖住不让魂魄被困留住
people would cover the mirrorsso the ghost wouldn't get trapped.
玛丽 死的时候那面镜子吸收了她的灵魂
Mary dies in front of a mirror, it draws in her spirit.
是的 可她怎么在100多个不同的镜子里来去自如
Yeah, but how can she move through, like, a hundred different mirrors?
我也不知道 如果那镜子是源头的话我建议我们找到并毁灭它
I don't know, but if the mirror's asource, I say we find it and smash it.
恩 我也不知道也许这样能行
Yeah, I don't know. Maybe.
你好
Hello.
查理
Charlie?
嘿
Hey.
嘿 没事了
Hey, it's okay.
你可以睁开你的眼睛了 查理
You can open up your eyes, Charlie.It's okay.
没事了
All right.
现在听着
Now, listen.
你就呆在床上别动
You're gonna stay right here, on this bed.
你别注视玻璃或者任何有反射的东西 好吗
And you're not gonna look at glass oranything else that has a reflection, okay?
只要你不那么做 她就无法靠近你。-
Now, as long as you do that, she cannot get you.
可我不能永远那样
But I can't keep that up forever.
我会死 是吗
I'm gonna die, aren't l?
不
No.
不 不会永远不会的
Not any time soon.
好吧 查理
All right, Charlie.
我们需要知道发生了什么
We need to know what happened.
我们在卫生间里 唐娜说了她的名字
We were in the bathroom.Donna said it.
这不是我想要问的
That's not what we're talking about.
有发生过些事情 是吗
Something happened, didn't it?
在你过去的生活里
In your life.
可能是个秘密…
A secret.
使某人受到伤害的秘密
Where someone got hurt.
你能告诉我们吗
Can you tell us about it?
我有过一个男朋友
I had this boyfriend.
我很爱他
I loved him…
但他有时候也让我害怕 你明白吗
but he kind of scared me too, you know?
在他家的一天夜里
And one night…
我们吵了起来
at his house, we got in this fight…
然后我说要分手
and I broke up with him.
他开始心烦意乱 他说他需要我
And he got upset, and he said he needed me…
他也很爱我
and he loved me.
他还说…
And he said.
「查理 如果你走出这个门 我就自杀」
"Charlie, if you walk out that doorright now, l'm gonna kill myself."
你知道我怎么回答的吗
And do you know what I said?
我说「随你便」
I said, "Go ahead."
我就离开了
And I left.
我怎么能那么说
How could I say that?
我怎么能那样离开他
How could I leave him like that?
我只是… …
I just.
我根本就不信他会那么做 你明白吗
I didn't believe him, you know?
可我应该相信他的
I should've.
你知道 她男朋友自杀了 但这不是查理的错
You know, her boyfriend killing himself, that's not really Charlie's fault.
根据我所知道的鬼魂可不能分辨这种情况
You know as well as I dospirits don't exactly see shades of gray.
迪恩 查理 有着使某人死亡的秘密
Dean, Charlie had a secret, someone died.
这对 玛丽来说就足够了
That's good enough for Mary.
我也这么猜
I guess.
你知道吗 我在想
You know, I've been thinking.
我们也许不应该把镜子摧毁
It might not be enoughto just smash that mirror.
为什么 你什么意思
Why? What do you mean?
这很难困住玛丽 不是吗 她从一面的镜子转到另一面镜子
Well, Mary's hard to pin down.She moves from mirror to mirror.
谁能说她只会一直呆在镜子里面呢 所以我们需要把她困住
So who's to say that she's not gonnajust keep hiding in them forever?
所以 也许
So maybe…
所以我们需要把她困住
we should try to pin her down.
你知道吗把她召唤到原来的镜子
You know, summon her to her mirror…
然后把她摧毁
and then smash it.
- 那好 你怎么知道那肯定有用 - 我不知道
- How do you know that's gonna work? - I don't.
我也不确定
Not for sure.
好的 谁来召唤她呢
Well, who's gonna summon her?
我来
I will.
她会跟着我来
She'll come after me.
好吧 你知道吗 这就是我要说的
All right, you know what? That's it.
这和杰西卡有关 是吗
This is about Jessica, isn't it?
你觉得这是你痛苦的秘密 某种意义上来说你杀了她
You think that's your dirty little secret?That you killed her somehow?
萨姆 你必须停止这么想 兄弟
Sam, this has gotta stop, man.
我是说 噩梦连连不停在梦里喊出她的名字
I mean, the nightmares and calling hername out in the middle of the night…
这会杀了你的
it's gonna kill you.
听我说
Now, listen to me.
这不是你错
It wasn't your fault.
如果你想怪罪谁那就怪罪杀害她的东西
If you wanna blame something, then blame the thing that killed her.
或者 你干嘛不痛扁我 是我把你从她身边带走的
Hell, why don't you take a swing at me.I dragged you away from her.
我不怪你
I don't blame you.
好的 你也不该怪你自己 因为对于她你无能为力
You shouldn't blame yourself.There's nothing you could've done.
- 可我能警告她 - 警告什么
- I could've warned her. - About what?
你根本就不知道会发生什么
You didn't know whatwas gonna happen.
还有 这根本就不是一个秘密 我也知道它
And besides, all of this isn't a secret.I mean, I know all about it.
它可能根本就不能吸引玛丽
It's not gonna work with Mary.
不 你不了解
No, you don't.
- 我不了解什么 - 你并不知道事情的全部
- I don't what? - You don't know all about it.
我有些事没告诉你
I haven't told you everything.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
如果我全都告诉你了 那就不是秘密了
Well, it wouldn't really be a secretif I told you, would it?
是的
No.
可是我不喜欢那样 不要再去想这法子了 忘记它
I don't like it. It's not gonna happen.Forget it.
迪恩 如果我们不做点什么
Dean, that girl back thereis going to die…
那个女孩就要死了 你知道吗
unless we do something about it.And you know what?
没人知道此后还有多少同样的人这么死去
Who knows how many more peopleare gonna die after that?
现在让我们来解决它
Now, we're doing this.
你必须让我那么做
You've got to let me do this.
好的 这太棒了
Well, that's just great.
那好吧 开始找吧
All right, let's start looking.
也许他们早就把它卖掉了
Maybe they've already sold it.
我可不那么认为
I don't think so.
找到它了
That's it.
你确定你要这么做
You sure about this?
镜子巫婆
Bloody Mary.
我出去看看 呆在这 小心点
I'll go check that out, you stay here.Be careful.
摧毁任何移动的东西
Smash anything that moves.
糟糕
Crap.
- 停住别动 - 伙计们
- Hold it! - Whoa, guys.
是假警报 我不小心触动的
False alarm. I tripped the system.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是老板的儿子
I'm the boss's kid.
你是阿姆西罗先生的儿子
You're Mr. Yamashiro's kid?
来吧
Come on.
进到这面镜子里来
Come into this one.
是你的错
It's your fault.
你杀了她
You killed her.
你杀了杰西卡
You killed Jessica.
- 就象我说的我是被收养的 - 是的
- Like I said, I was adopted. - Yeah.
你知道吗 我真的 我现在真的没时间
You know, I just I really don'thave time for this right now.
你从来都没告诉她真相 你到底是谁
You never told her the truth, who you really were.
可不止这些 不是吗
But it's more than that, isn't it?
你做的那些关于
Those nightmares you've been having…
杰西卡死亡的噩梦
of Jessica dying…
尖叫
screaming…
燃烧
burning.
在她死前 你是有时间的
You had them for daysbefore she died.
不是吗
Didn't you?
你那么无情的忽略这一切
You were so desperate to be normal…
只相信那只是梦境
to believe they were just dreams.
你怎么能忽视这些梦
How could you ignore them like that?
你怎么能就让她这么死去
How could you leave her alone to die?
你已经梦到它会发生
You dreamt it would happen!
萨姆 萨姆
Sammy? Sammy?
是萨姆
It's Sam.
- 天那 你还好吧 - 恩 还好
- God. You okay? - Yeah.
来吧 来
Come on, come on.
是你杀了他们
You killed them.
所有这些人
All those people.
是你杀了他们
You killed them.
嘿 萨姆
Hey, Sam?
嗯
Yeah?
看来我们要倒600年的霉了
This has gotta be like, what, 600 years bad luck?
这一切真的结束了吗
So this is really over?
是的 结束了
Yeah, it's over.
谢谢你
Thank you.
理查
Charlie.
你男朋友的死
Your boyfriend's death…
你应该原谅你自己
You really should tryto forgive yourself.
无论你做了什么 你可能不能阻止它
No matter what you did, you probably couldn't have stopped it.
有时不好的事情还是会发生
Sometimes bad things just happen.
这是个好的建议
That's good advice.
嘿 萨姆
Hey, Sam?
嗯
Yeah?
现在这都结束了
Now that this is all over…
我想知道你的秘密
l want you to tell mewhat that secret was.
听着
Look.
你是我的大哥
You're my brother…
我可以为你死
and l'd die for you.
但有些秘密我还是要保留
But there are some thingsI need to keep to myself.